ANDRES SAENZ

101 North Mockingbird Circle, Cedar Creek, TX 78612 ◆ C: 512-304-5775 ◆ andresgsaenz@gmail.com

https://github.com/saenza76 ♦ http://www.andressaenz.me

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer specializing in Front-End Development. Recent graduate of The Coding Bootcamp at The University of Texas at Austin. Successful at presenting and advocating for design concepts. Enjoys learning new languages and frameworks to better skill set.

SKILLS

- Front-End Web Development
- Back-End Web Development
- Web Design

- Customer Service
- Data management
- Troubleshooting and debugging

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Strong: HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Github, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose Experienced: MySQL, React, Angular, AJAX, API's, Handlebars, Sequelize, PHP

- EDUCATION

Certificate: Full Stack Web Development, 2017 University of Texas at Austin - Austin, TX

The UT Austin Coding Bootcamp is a competitive, 24-week full stack development program that trains students to become web developers. UT Austin Coding Bootcamp supports student success through graduation and job placement.

WORK HISTORY

Specialist, 12/2015 to Current

Apple – Austin, TX

- Identified and solved technical issues with a variety of diagnostic tools.
- Handled all customer relations issues in a gracious manner and in accordance with company policies.
- Educated customers about the brand to incite excitement about the company's mission and values.
- Consistently hit and exceeded sales goals.

Lead Teller, 07/2013 to 12/2015

Wells Fargo – Austin, TX

- Assessed clients' financial situations to develop strategic financial planning solutions.
- Prioritized daily workflows, including all inbound calls, quotes and sales-related inquiries.
- Exceeded team sales goals by 200%.

Cashier. 06/2010 to 05/2013

HEB – Bastrop, TX

- Developed positive customer relationships through friendly greetings and excellent service.
- Answered questions regarding the store and its merchandise.
- Trained and served as a peer coach for new sales associates.